Some people question it now.
Is it good rain?
Is there rain coming and no thunder?
Well, you know they're controlling the weather.
Well, maybe.
Yeah, man, they're controlling the weather.
Yeah, maybe.
So fake weather, fake storms?
Yes.
Ready?
They control it with frequency.
You know, you can't see the radio waves, but you know there's waves.
That's frequency.
So they control the weather with frequency.
So, for instance, like, you know right now, well, yeah, scientists and government.
So, you know, they have the war going on in Iran.
And so Iran took out a number of the U.S. bases that were around.
So they had U.S. bases in Saudi Arabia, in Kuwait, in the UAE, you know, Dubai.
And Iran attacked all of them.
When Iran attacked all of them, all of a sudden, rain came back to Mesopotamia, to Egypt, to Iraq, etc.
They had had a drought for, like, 20 years.
And the minute they bust up the U.S. bases, water come, and now it's starting to grow again.
Immediately.
Because, you know, there's only a month or two.
Immediately, it's starting to rain, and the rain just coming and coming and coming.
And because folks have theorized that they were using frequencies to drought, to create a famine.
So, when they say the weather is forming in Africa, and it comes into Grenada,
and it's a part of the system?
Yeah, man.
They're controlling everything.
That's why we have to break it up.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Well, we have to take the strength from the most high to beat the most low.
That's the power.
But that's why we have to understand the land.
Right.
You know, so people like you sharing and teaching us, you know, it's so important,
because the land has all of this knowledge and information and energy,
and how it's using the energy to do this and that.
And we, as humans, need to be doing the same thing.
So, why didn't you use the energy to clean up the environment?
I call it to put it clean up the environment.
Because people are trying to do that, but the people...
I'm not going to say that.
Okay.
But people do it.
Men do those things, but they can't undo it.
It's only going to...
Yeah.
And they don't want to undo it, because they're obsessed with power and making money.
You know?
But that's not going to last.
That's not going to last.
It can't last.
It's not sustainable.
You're going to see...
Remember I said it, huh?
So that you can remember...
I remember when Amanda told me that.
There's going to be another war.
And when that war finish, it's going to rain and rain and rain and rain and rain.
Because the earth is going to be restoring.
And all of the things that had been put...
All of the machinery and technology that had been put in place to try and disrupt the
way the earth exists, it's gone.
And the earth will restore.
Remember during COVID, how they said, how you see all the animals start to come out and
you know, everything started to replenish once humans got out of the way?
That's the thing.
But you know, people who know the earth, that's what we're supposed to do.
Humans are supposed to be in community with the earth.
But they're trying to control it.
So remember I said it, there's going to be a big war.
The war is going to be the people of the world rising up and they're going to attack
all of them.
And then there's going to be a big rain and we're going to see things grow again.
And people like you are going to be very...
We're going to be appreciative to people like you because you're teaching us how to grow
it.
So thank you.
You're welcome.
Speaking the truth at all times to all people.
My new album, Truth Translator, drops June 14th.
It's not a movement, it's movement music.